export const CROWN_DATA = [
  {
    id: 'war1',
    name: 'War or Peace',
    isActive: true,
    questionsArray: [
      {
        id: 'war1',
        options: [
          'Direct assault on the besieging forces.',
          'Undermining morale through starvation and endurance.',
          'Evacuating the fortress and negotiating a peace treaty.        ',
        ],
        question:
          'What strategy is best for defending a fortress during a prolonged siege?',
        correct: 'Undermining morale through starvation and endurance.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war2',
        options: [
          'Providing regular victories.',
          'Ensuring adequate supplies and rest.',
          'Maintaining strict discipline.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a key element of maintaining morale among troops during a long campaign?',
        correct: 'Ensuring adequate supplies and rest.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war3',
        options: [
          'Form alliances and seek mutual support.',
          'Engage in diplomatic negotiations to avoid conflict.',
          'Focus solely on military preparations, ignoring diplomacy.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you manage relations with neighboring states if you are preparing for a major conflict?',
        correct: 'Form alliances and seek mutual support.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war4',
        options: [
          'Use them to spread disinformation among enemy ranks.',
          'Gather intelligence on enemy troop movements and strategies.',
          'Deploy them to sabotage enemy resources directly.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the most effective way to utilize spies during wartime?',
        correct: 'Gather intelligence on enemy troop movements and strategies.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war5',
        options: [
          'The size and strength of the attacking army.',
          'The fortifications and defenses of the besieged location.',
          'The weather conditions during the siege.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a crucial factor in the success of a siege warfare strategy?',
        correct: 'The fortifications and defenses of the besieged location.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war6',
        options: [
          'Use heavy artillery to breach the walls.',
          'Starve out the defenders by cutting off supplies.',
          'Offer a generous surrender deal to the defenders.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is an effective method to break a siege if you are the attacker?',
        correct: 'Starve out the defenders by cutting off supplies.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war7',
        options: [
          'Focus on building more weapons and armor.',
          'Invest in fortifications and defensive structures.',
          'Balance resources between offense and defense.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you allocate resources during a prolonged military campaign?',
        correct: 'Focus on building more weapons and armor.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war8',
        options: [
          "Increase your own propaganda efforts to counteract the enemy's.",
          'Focus on military victories to overshadow enemy messages.',
          'Engage in diplomatic efforts to discredit enemy propaganda.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best way to counteract enemy propaganda during a war?',
        correct:
          "Increase your own propaganda efforts to counteract the enemy's.",
      },
      {
        id: 'war9',
        options: [
          'Use messenger pigeons and couriers.',
          'Establish a network of signal fires and beacons.',
          'Maintain constant verbal updates through regular meetings.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you ensure effective communication with your generals during a campaign?',
        correct: 'Use messenger pigeons and couriers.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war10',
        options: [
          'The terrain and natural obstacles.',
          'The number of enemy troops.',
          'The timing of the battle.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a critical consideration when planning a defensive battle strategy?',
        correct: 'The terrain and natural obstacles.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war11',
        options: [
          'Mobilize all available troops immediately.',
          "Send scouts to gather information on the enemy's strength.",
          'Evacuate civilians and focus on defensive positions.',
        ],
        question: 'How should you respond to a surprise attack by the enemy?',
        correct: 'Mobilize all available troops immediately.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war12',
        options: [
          'High morale boosts performance and resilience.',
          'Morale has little impact on actual combat effectiveness.',
          'Low morale can be overcome with additional training.',
        ],
        question:
          'What role does morale play in the effectiveness of your troops?',
        correct: 'High morale boosts performance and resilience.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war13',
        options: [
          'Position troops on high ground for a tactical advantage.',
          'Use natural obstacles to hinder enemy movement.',
          'Avoid complex terrain to maintain mobility.',
        ],
        question: 'How can you use terrain to your advantage in battle?',
        correct: 'Position troops on high ground for a tactical advantage.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war14',
        options: [
          'Execute them to set an example.',
          'Offer incentives to those who stay loyal.',
          'Investigate the reasons for desertion and address underlying issues.',
        ],
        question: 'What is the best way to handle deserters in your army?',
        correct: 'Execute them to set an example.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war15',
        options: [
          'Establish reliable supply lines and stockpiles.',
          'Rely on local resources and foraging.',
          'Negotiate supply agreements with allies.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you ensure that your army is well-supplied during a campaign?',
        correct: 'Establish reliable supply lines and stockpiles.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war16',
        options: [
          'The weather and sea conditions.',
          'The number of enemy ships.',
          'The speed of your vessels.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is an important consideration when planning a naval engagement?',
        correct: 'The weather and sea conditions.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war17',
        options: [
          'Rotate troops to reduce fatigue and losses.',
          'Focus on quick, decisive battles to avoid prolonged engagements.',
          'Increase recruitment to replace lost soldiers.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you address the issue of attrition in your forces?',
        correct: 'Rotate troops to reduce fatigue and losses.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war18',
        options: [
          'To breach fortifications and walls.',
          'To transport troops and supplies.',
          'To create a psychological impact on the defenders.',
        ],
        question: 'What is the primary purpose of constructing siege engines?',
        correct: 'To breach fortifications and walls.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war19',
        options: [
          'Secure military aid and joint operations.',
          'Focus on economic and trade agreements.',
          'Establish cultural and diplomatic ties.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you leverage alliances to strengthen your military position?',
        correct: 'Secure military aid and joint operations.',
      },
      {
        id: 'war20',
        options: [
          'Release them to foster goodwill and future negotiations.',
          'Use them as forced labor for your war efforts.',
          'Integrate them into your own forces if feasible.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best strategy for managing captured enemy soldiers?',
        correct: 'Release them to foster goodwill and future negotiations.',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'tax1',
    name: 'Peasant Rebellion',
    isActive: true,
    questionsArray: [
      {
        id: 'tax1',
        options: [
          'Increase taxes for the wealthy and nobility.',
          'Uniform taxation across all social classes.',
          'Introduce new taxes on luxury goods.',
        ],
        question:
          'What tax approach is most effective for maintaining the economy during wartime?',
        correct: 'Introduce new taxes on luxury goods.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax2',
        options: [
          'Implement gradual increases to avoid sudden shocks.',
          'Ensure transparency and fairness in tax collection.',
          'Provide incentives for compliance.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you ensure that new tax policies do not lead to widespread unrest?',
        correct: 'Ensure transparency and fairness in tax collection.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax3',
        options: [
          'Implementing immediate and visible improvements in public services.',
          'Providing clear communication about the reasons for the tax increases.',
          'Offering tax breaks to specific groups.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a critical component of managing public dissatisfaction with tax increases?',
        correct:
          'Providing clear communication about the reasons for the tax increases.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax4',
        options: [
          'Cut funding to non-essential government programs.',
          'Increase taxes on all income levels.',
          'Seek loans from wealthy merchants or neighboring kingdoms.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you balance the budget when facing a fiscal deficit during a war?',
        correct: 'Cut funding to non-essential government programs.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax5',
        options: [
          'Diversify the economy by investing in various sectors.',
          'Focus on expanding military expenditures to ensure security.',
          'Prioritize short-term gains to address immediate financial needs.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best approach to maintaining long-term economic stability?',
        correct: 'Diversify the economy by investing in various sectors.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax6',
        options: [
          'Provide subsidies and support to affected businesses.',
          'Increase taxes on businesses to fund the war effort.',
          'Implement price controls to stabilize the market.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you address the economic impact of war on local businesses?',
        correct: 'Provide subsidies and support to affected businesses.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax7',
        options: [
          'Control the supply of money in circulation.',
          'Increase interest rates to reduce borrowing.',
          'Implement wage controls and rationing.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is an effective strategy for managing inflation during wartime?',
        correct: 'Control the supply of money in circulation.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax8',
        options: [
          'Implement progressive tax rates based on income levels.',
          'Use a flat tax rate for simplicity.',
          'Provide exemptions for certain groups.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you ensure fairness in the distribution of tax burdens?',
        correct: 'Implement progressive tax rates based on income levels.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax9',
        options: [
          'Use public speeches and media announcements.',
          'Directly address concerns through town hall meetings.',
          'Issue official decrees and written statements.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best way to communicate the need for tax increases to the public?',
        correct: 'Use public speeches and media announcements.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax10',
        options: [
          'Prioritize essential services and public welfare.',
          'Allocate funds based on political influence.',
          'Focus on debt repayment and interest obligations.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you manage the allocation of government funds during a crisis?',
        correct: 'Prioritize essential services and public welfare.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax11',
        options: [
          'It builds trust and reduces resistance to policy changes.',
          'It has little impact on public perception.',
          'It can lead to political challenges and opposition.',
        ],
        question:
          'What role does transparency play in managing public finances?',
        correct: 'It builds trust and reduces resistance to policy changes.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax12',
        options: [
          'Implement strict oversight and auditing procedures.',
          'Increase penalties for corrupt practices.',
          'Encourage anonymous reporting of corruption.',
        ],
        question: 'How can you address potential corruption in tax collection?',
        correct: 'Implement strict oversight and auditing procedures.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax13',
        options: [
          'Engage in dialogue and negotiate with protest leaders.',
          'Use law enforcement to disperse the crowds.',
          'Implement immediate policy changes to address concerns.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best approach to handling large-scale public protests against tax policies?',
        correct: 'Engage in dialogue and negotiate with protest leaders.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax14',
        options: [
          'Provide targeted financial aid and social programs.',
          'Implement broad-based economic stimulus measures.',
          'Increase public works projects to create jobs.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you support the most vulnerable populations during economic hardships?',
        correct: 'Provide targeted financial aid and social programs.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax15',
        options: [
          'Offer incentives for early payment and compliance.',
          'Implement strict enforcement and penalties for non-compliance.',
          'Simplify tax procedures to reduce administrative burdens.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best way to encourage compliance with new tax policies?',
        correct: 'Offer incentives for early payment and compliance.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax16',
        options: [
          'Increase audits and enforcement actions.',
          'Provide amnesty periods for voluntary disclosure.',
          'Reduce tax rates to encourage compliance.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you address the issue of tax evasion during wartime?',
        correct: 'Increase audits and enforcement actions.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax17',
        options: [
          'Use economic modeling and simulations.',
          'Rely on historical data and trends.',
          'Consult with financial experts and advisors.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is an effective method for forecasting economic impacts of tax changes?',
        correct: 'Use economic modeling and simulations.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax18',
        options: [
          'Demonstrate clear and measurable outcomes from the reforms.',
          'Rely on media campaigns and public relations.',
          'Conduct regular surveys and feedback sessions.',
        ],
        question: 'How can you improve public confidence in economic reforms?',
        correct: 'Demonstrate clear and measurable outcomes from the reforms.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax19',
        options: [
          'Negotiate debt relief and restructuring agreements.',
          'Increase taxes to service the debt.',
          'Cut government spending and programs.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best way to manage government debt during a financial crisis?',
        correct: 'Negotiate debt relief and restructuring agreements.',
      },
      {
        id: 'tax20',
        options: [
          'Focus on military and defense expenditures.',
          'Allocate resources to economic recovery and development.',
          'Balance spending between defense and public welfare.',
        ],
        question: 'How should you prioritize government spending during a war?',
        correct: 'Focus on military and defense expenditures.',
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: 'royal',
    name: 'The Royal Heir',
    isActive: true,
    questionsArray: [
      {
        id: 'succession1',
        options: [
          'A) Rapid transfer of power to the successor with military support.',
          'B) Conduct a lengthy transitional period with political consultations.',
          'C) Strengthen legal succession by forming alliances with neighboring kingdoms.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best approach to ensure a smooth transition of power?',
        correct:
          'C) Strengthen legal succession by forming alliances with neighboring kingdoms.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession2',
        options: [
          'A) Provide them with hands-on experience in governance.',
          'B) Educate them through formal training and advisory councils.',
          'C) Allow them to make decisions and learn from their mistakes.',
        ],
        question: 'How can you prepare your heir for leadership effectively?',
        correct: 'A) Provide them with hands-on experience in governance.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession3',
        options: [
          'A) Demonstrating strong leadership skills and decisiveness.',
          'B) Building personal relationships with the nobility.',
          'C) Providing financial incentives and privileges.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a key factor in ensuring the successor gains the support of the nobility?',
        correct: 'A) Demonstrating strong leadership skills and decisiveness.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession4',
        options: [
          'A) Secure public endorsement through a formal ceremony.',
          'B) Address and resolve any legal disputes regarding succession.',
          'C) Strengthen the successor’s position through military demonstrations.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you address potential challenges to the successor’s legitimacy?',
        correct: 'A) Secure public endorsement through a formal ceremony.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession5',
        options: [
          'A) Implement reforms that address current issues and gain popular support.',
          'B) Increase military presence and security measures.',
          'C) Conduct a thorough review of the kingdom’s laws and governance structure.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the most effective way to maintain stability during the succession process?',
        correct:
          'A) Implement reforms that address current issues and gain popular support.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession6',
        options: [
          'A) Provide training in diplomatic negotiations and statecraft.',
          'B) Engage them in foreign policy discussions and negotiations.',
          'C) Rely on experienced diplomats to guide the successor.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you ensure that your successor is prepared to handle foreign diplomacy?',
        correct:
          'A) Provide training in diplomatic negotiations and statecraft.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession7',
        options: [
          'A) It influences the acceptance and legitimacy of the new ruler.',
          'B) It has minimal impact on the actual governance.',
          'C) It can be managed through media and propaganda.',
        ],
        question:
          'What role does public perception play in the succession process?',
        correct:
          'A) It influences the acceptance and legitimacy of the new ruler.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession8',
        options: [
          'A) Seek to unite factions through compromise and negotiation.',
          'B) Suppress dissenting factions to maintain control.',
          'C) Align with the most powerful faction for support.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you manage internal political factions during the succession?',
        correct:
          'A) Seek to unite factions through compromise and negotiation.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession9',
        options: [
          'A) Providing them with military training and experience.',
          'B) Ensuring they have strong diplomatic skills.',
          'C) Focusing on their strategic and financial acumen.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is a crucial aspect of preparing the successor for military leadership?',
        correct: 'A) Providing them with military training and experience.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession10',
        options: [
          'A) Facilitate open dialogue and negotiations.',
          'B) Replace advisors who are resistant to the successor.',
          'C) Strengthen the successor’s authority through decrees.',
        ],
        question:
          'How can you address potential conflicts between the successor and influential advisors?',
        correct: 'A) Facilitate open dialogue and negotiations.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession11',
        options: [
          'A) Maintain existing policies and structures.',
          'B) Implement immediate changes to align with the successor’s vision.',
          'C) Consult with previous advisors to guide the transition.',
        ],
        question:
          'What is the best way to ensure continuity in governance during the transition period?',
        correct:
          'B) Implement immediate changes to align with the successor’s vision.',
      },
      {
        id: 'succession12',
        options: [
          'A) Offer them positions of power or influence.',
          'B) Use legal and political means to neutralize their claims.',
          'C) Seek to reconcile and integrate them into the ruling structure.',
        ],
        question:
          'How should you handle opposition from rival claimants to the throne?',
        correct: 'B) Use legal and political means to neutralize their claims.',
      },
    ],
  },
];
